RG 023, State Teachers' Retirement Board
Connecticut State Library
- Series 4. Refund Check Registers, 1931-1966; 6 cubic feet
  - 2009-003, 6 cubic feet
    Items 32-33 are titled "Withdrawal Journal". Items 34-38 are titled "Refund Warrants". Individual pages in Item 32 are titled "Withdrawal Journal". Individual pages in Item 33 are titled "Withdrawal Journal" to January 1939 and starting in February 1939 are titled "Refund Check Register".
    - 1931 August 15 - 1936 June 25, 1 volume (Box Item 32)
    - 1936 July 1 - 1941 June 16, 1 volume (Box Item 33)
    - 1941 July 1 - 1946 June 15, 1 volume (Box Item 34)
    - 1946 July 1 - 1949 June 15, 1 volume (Box Item 35)
    - 1949 July 1 - 1951 June 15, 1 volume (Box Item 36)
    - 1951 July - 1953 June, 1 volume (Box Item 37)
    - 1953 July - 1955 June, 1 volume (Box Item 38)
    - 1955 July - 1957 June, 1 volume (Box Item 39)
    - 1957 July - 1958 November, 1 volume (Box Item 40)
    - 1958 November - 1960 June, 1 volume (Box Item 41)
    - 1960 July - 1961 June, 1 volume (Box Item 42)
    - 1961 July - 1963 June, 1 volume (Box Item 43)
    - 1963 July - 1965 June, 1 volume (Box Item 44)
    - 1965 July - 1966 August, 1 volume (Box Item 45)